Oh, it's turtle paper, isn't it?
What?
Just a minute.
I'll get right on it.
I'm about to show my unfriendliness.
Oh-ho!
Oh, wow!
It's like I've just caught a tuna.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Kaho Kobayashi, attendance number 11 of the C to B group.
Yes, that's right.
Last time, we made benches and wood tables using saws and screws.
I made a bench and a wood table using a saw and screws.
This time, I would like to DIY this wallpaper.
But as you can see, I'm empty-handed.
As you can see, I'm empty-handed.
I don't have any tools.
I'm thinking of going out to buy some stuff after this.
I like this video.
We've just started.
If you like it...
If you like it, please click the "Good" button or "Like" button.
Please subscribe to our channel.
And please leave lots of comments.
I'm going to go buy some stuff.
I'm off!
So, this time, I'm going to visit the corner of 3points, Incomplete Point.
I'm going to buy some things that I'm interested in, such as painting goods, weather, and so on, at Sukkuru.
I'm going to go shopping for some things I'm interested in.
Log Log DIY!
So this is the DIY corner.
Cute!
This is like masking tape.
What? What is this?
I've never seen tape of this size before.
You can stick it on the wallpaper and peel it off.
Ah! So this is something you can put on the wall.
Just tear it off by hand and stick it on.
It's going to be so cute!
I want some!
I want one.
Do you have this one too?
Ah! There are so many kinds.
Tiles and stuff.
You can see them all over here.
I wonder if they're all stickers, like the ones we've been looking at.
What? I want one.
This is a wall photo.
You can put a sticker on the wall and peel it off.
I didn't know you could put pictures on the wall.
On the wall.
Oh, my God.
What? Wait a minute.
I'm about to show my lack of friends.
What's this?
Remake sheet.
What's a "remake sheet"? You stick it on and peel it off.
It's a higher grade remake sheet.
You can put it on anything.
If you put the Remake Sheet on something like this...
You can make something more original.
You can put it on helmets and stuff.
So it's cute?
We made helmets last time.
I did.
What about the towering ones?
What did you think? Did you get a response?
I got a lot of feedback.
Fans told me they saw it.
They said, "You look good.
It's so refreshing to see you DIY.
It's not something they see very often.
They said it was a lot of fun.
I bought a few pieces and put them together.
and put them together.
It's cute, isn't it?
It looks like the Golden Pavilion.
It's like the Temple of the Golden Pavilion.
gold clothes and food
The yellow color looks a little fluorescent.
This
In case you're wondering, it's yellow from the image
I'm going to use one of these checks and
and a pink one from this argyle-like
but something about this
I'm interested in this tile.
I don't know if I'll use it.
I don't know if I'm going to use it, but I'd like to try it out.
I'd like to try it out.
I'd like to leave here with this set of four for now.
I'd like to leave here with this four-piece set.
I'm not sure if this has anything to do with it at all, but I'm curious about Gorilla for adhesion.
I'm going to buy some Gorilla Tape later.
It has so much impact that I want to buy it.
It's so long!
I've never seen a tree before.
I've never seen one this big, only at a bungee jumping place or something like that.
Oh, interesting. This one?
Clang! Clang!
Clang. Carabiner.
It doesn't look like a carabiner.It doesn't look like a carabiner, does it?
I've been calling it "Gachan." It's "Carabiner.
I've been calling it "Carabiner" for a long time.
I remember. I think this is the painting area.
I'm sure this is the painting area.
I've always wanted to try it. I'm looking forward to it.
There it is.
It looks like they use rollers like this.
I wonder if it has anything to do with the hardness.
I wonder if it has anything to do with the hardness of the rollers, or if it's just a matter of getting a bigger one.
I'll put it in once.
And, uh, what color should I use?
And, uh, what color should I make it?
They're active in tuning.
I thought it would be nice if we could use some of the old member colors.
So...
So, about this size...
I'll choose a size like this.
Yellow.
Yellow, then this one.
This yellow.
Number three.
Mayuma.
Mayuma-san is purple, so a little bit of purple.
No purple?
I don't have any purple.
I'll mix it!
I'll mix it so red and
Red is...
Um...
Recently, recently, a year ago
I joined
Sakuragi's color is
Red
I'll get it.
And then
Next, blue.
Blue is the color of the whole tree.
Since it is together with
Blue
Oh, there are different kinds of blue.
There are different kinds of blue.
Light blue
Light blue and
blue
But there's an in-between.
What?
But I think blue would be better here.
I decided to go with blue.
And, Mayuma's purple is made by mixing blue and red.
And this green...
What do you call this?
Wakagusa
Lime? Light green.
There's pink and orange.
This one...
I'm going to use gentle pink and gentle orange.
They are strong girls themselves, but they have an image of clear colors.
But this time, we're going to use gentle colors.
Next, white.
There are various kinds of white, ivory, milky white, and white.
I'm curious, so I'm going to choose milky white.
Now, nine colors.
One, two, three, four, nine colors. I've been studying a lot.
I've been studying a lot. This is the one that makes you beautiful, right?
I've never done this before.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wow.
This is gonna be beautiful.
I'm not buying it this time.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
You know, the crew that builds the stage for the show, the props people, mainly...
When I told them that I was on a DIY YouTube channel, they let me use the impact driver.
He gave me a pair of leather gloves and told me I could use them, so I put them on and shuffled around.
I put them on and swoosh, swoosh, swoosh. What a set!
I hit a few screws. Yay!
I was overflowing with joy. I'm on tour now, but when I go to other venues, I'll be waiting with leather gloves on.
I'm thinking that if I put on the leather gloves and stand by, they'll let me do it again.
Oh, the wallpaper... here it is!
Oh!
Here...
It's wallpaper.
Roll 15?
There are 15 rolls.
15 meter rolls.
I forgot to put 15 meters on.
I've never seen wallpaper wrapped around anything before.
Hold it.
What?
It's heavy!
I thought it was light! Wallpaper?
It's so heavy!
That's why I've never held it.
It's like fishing for a tuna.
I'll have someone strong hold it for me later.
I didn't know that.
Okay, so...
For now, what you need isIn the meantime, we have everything we need.
I've got everything I need.
Go to the cashier as soon as you can.
I'm going to get it!
It's a very, very personal thing.
I feel like buying some gorilla paper and glue.
I'll buy them!
I just had to have it.
I really want it.
I don't know where I'm going to use it. I haven't decided yet, but I'm going to buy it.
I don't know where I'm going to use it yet, but I'm going to buy it.
So I bought what I need!
I've never held so many things with both hands before!
But it's heavy!
That's all I bought!
And I've never been to a home improvement store before.
I did a lot of backwork just looking around.
And I was able to buy some Gorilla Tape.
I really had a great time.
I thought, "If I see a home improvement store on a regular outing, I'd like to go in there.
It was fun.
I'm going to go back now and start working on the wall!
So, if you liked this video, please subscribe and like our channel.
If you enjoyed this video, please subscribe, like, and comment!
Lastly, I'd like to introduce a product I recommend for the hot season!
A long-awaited new flavor of soda has been added to the popular series of salt fever supplements that do not dissolve even in the hottest places!
Quick charge of electrolytes in a can to prevent heat stroke!
In addition, Salt Fever Candy Pro comes in three flavors: lemon, plum, and acerola, so you'll never get tired of taking it!
Please check out the overview section!